

Samet Sunman *Full Stack Developer*

🕥 github.com/sametsunman 🚗 A2, B 🛗 09/12/1995 🚳 Single

OBJECTIVE

Hello there, I am 26 years old. Technology have been in my life since I was a kid and I have always loved anything related with computer. I started to code and design at a very young age. Most of my skills and knowledge are self-taugh. I've studied Computer Engineering at Duzce University. During my study I was in Erasmus+ student exchange program at Lublin University of Technology in Poland for one semester. I have successfully completed all my courses and graduated. In the summer of 2017, I did my first internship at Boyner Büyük Mağazacılık A.Ş. in the information technology department as a software intern. In summer of 2018, I completed my second internship at General Mobile's mobile application development unit. I had worked at Ajans Press Group for more than 2 years -since March 2019. I started to work at Yves Rocher Turkey in December 2021. I know C#, Java and Kotlin languages. Also I've expeirence in .NET Core, React and Angular Frameworks.

EDUCATION

(ANADOLU UNIVERSITY

Management Information Systems
Open Education System

100 LUBLIN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

Computer Science
Erasmus+ Student Exchange Programme with GPA 3.75

DUZCE UNIVERSITYComputer Engineering

Obtained the BS degree with GPA 2.86

09/2019 – present Eskisehir, Turkey

09/2018 - 02/2019

Lublin, Poland

09/2013 - 02/2019

Duzce, Turkey

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

® YVES ROCHER

Software Developer

- New Mobile Application (React Native, Typescript)
- Old Mobile Application (Ionic, Javascript)
 - · Added new features
 - Performance improvements
 - User interface improvements
 - · Published Play Store and App Store
- Backoffice Services (PHP)
 - Created new api services for mobile applications
 - · Developed api service versions

¶AJANS PRESS

Software Engineer

- Muletools (Asp.NET MVC)
 - · Designed new pages
 - Set CRUD operations
- Medya Bilgi Bankası (React, Javascript)
 - Designed web application
- Backoffice Web (React, Typescript)
 - Designed web application
 - · Created forms, tables
- Backoffice Services (.NET Core)
 - · Created Restful API Services
 - Written SQL queries
- Newscope (React, Typescript)
 - Built structure
 - · Created components
 - Entegrated web APIs

GENERAL MOBILE

Mobile Application Development Intern

- Burn Dollars Game (Java, Javascript)
 - · Used javascript game engine
 - · Designed game assets
 - Published on Google Play
- Movie Guide App (Kotlin)
 - Developed Application
 - Published on Google Play

BOYNER

Software Development Intern

- Boyner Blog (Html, JavaScript)
 - Developed new modules for Joomla blog based
- Intelligence game (Windows Forms)
 - · Created 5 different game level
- Car Race (Asp.NET, Html, JavaScript)
 - Designed game with Html and JavaScript
 - · Converted to multiplayer game using SignalR

11/2021 – present Şişli, İstanbul

03/2019 - 11/2021

Kadıköy, İstanbul

08/2017 - 09/2017 Sarıyer, İstanbul

08/2018 - 09/2018

Şişli, İstanbul



TurkishEnglishPolishNativeB2 - Upper IntermediateA1 - Beginner

COURSES

React Native Bootcamp
Kodluyoruz

11/2020 - 01/2021
Online

High-Level Android Programming with JavaiSMEK

03/2019 - 06/2019
Fatih, istanbul

Web Programming with .Net Core and Multitier Architecture15MEK
03/2019 - 06/2019
Fatih

ORGANISATIONS

Patika Front-End Challenge 04/2021 - 05/2021 Mentor Online

SKILLS

ExperiencesWebsite Development (Backend,Frontend)
Mobile Application
Desktop Application

Frameworks
.NET Core, .NET Framework, ReactJS, VueJS

IDEVisual Studio, Android Studio, Eclipse, Visual
Studio Code

Languages *C#, C++, Java, Kotlin, Go, Javascript, Typescript*

Databases

MsSQL, Oracle Sql, Sqlite, Mongodb, Firebase

Style Libraries & PreprocessorsBootstrap, Material UI, Styled Components, SCSS

Other Technologies

Git, Oop, N-tier Architecture, Entity Framework, LINQ, REST API, Npm, Redux, Axios

INTERESTS

 Movie, Music, Reading, Cycling

REFERENCES

References available on request